Hello friends, in today's video we are going to
talk
about the signature policy. If you
want to buy a policy, then definitely watch this video till the end. Let's
try to find out about the benefits of this policy. If this is a policy of this type, then you should get
25% approval. Signature policy. You
can purchase this policy online, but if you are
investing in it, then know that
this policy is not an addition policy or an
enrollment policy. From this point of view,
you are basically investing in the share market. So
whatever money you are investing,
your money is going to be invested in the market. So
in this policy, let me
tell you in detail
what are the special benefits of this policy. Like,
after purchasing it, it is given to the life insurance company.
Okay, interpolation, whatever policy you have added,
all this is
given to the life insurance company for so many years. Inter premium
without any dictionary download. Okay, so when
you pay the premium of the new policy, there is no
allocation charge in it.
Your entire money is invested in the market.
Special benefits. So
what happens in the Udaan policy?  Whenever you invest money in
this land with the company,
what does the company do after paying a premium of 1 lakh? There are
two questions. If you are paying 1% of Rs. 1 lakh, then they
take ₹2000/- or ₹410 from you and the
conscience is that it is fully appointed on this post
but to get it you have to pass a minimum qualification
in every field. Okay, now once the
school is over, then you will get the
score, that is,
how much booster is there, what
benefit do you get further, so we are going to see the
return of motor
cars and policy admission charge. The
policy will be complete, whatever you have
purchased from us, then the expiry date will be fixed. Subscribe
and
subscribe.
Subscribe and
subscribe. If you subscribe, then subscribe to this channel.
I can give you a written assurance. Okay,
and the benefit means
you can take this policy for 10 years or 25 years
or you
can take production till your life is not over. In this plant, you have a
clear feasibility option, like you
mix it, there are different
portfolio things in it.  Like if there is positive
energy, if the police are
accused, then if you
subscribe, how will we manage it, then
if it is
over, then you
can subscribe or if the
entire subscription is over, then you can take it from the
plan, from which
you have to
take it completely, if you subscribe to it, then
subscribe
to it,
like I have given you a return subscription,
subscribe to my channel,
you have subscribed and you have
taken the payment, if you
subscribe, that is,
all the premiums of the number of years you have used, only then
you will get this model recharge
in the fund of the association, and in mobile recharges, you
can ask for it if you have not subscribed in the market, that is, you should subscribe, that is, if you
subscribe to it, then you
mean,
school
subscribe, that is, the
price of the share on the amount,
you must invest some money in the share market,
buy shares of Sharma Ramesh company, then you get numbers and for how much
time, this point is this point
and you will get numbers, in this you will get the number of
units, so the money that you get
in the market if there is a
pregnant person, then you are getting
appointed on that, which
This point of the market, this point is
subscribed, now it is for the quarter, whatever the
present value of the fund will be, it
gives you 3.25 subscription, okay, to
avail these benefits, you have to subscribe
to the card, minimum 10 channel subscription,
okay,
subscribe now, this
subscription about the subscriber, if you
can
subscribe to this then
you will have for the life options, whole your
options limit purchases, okay, the maximum
annual minimum body system is given, it is
10 years or till then
you can take it, okay, this is the minimum body
system, if you are
subscribing then you have to
subscribe,
but
in the production of subscription, there is
no specific policy premium available for any doctor, if you want to buy any new
k, then okay, you
can take the paid payment, if you are
less than zero, whatever your
pregnancy time
is, and if you
subscribe then
you feel that I can
take more time in less time, but if you do
not subscribe then you should subscribe to this
channel  To
subscribe
subscribe to that is a little department
so it is taken in a bond okay if there is a hole that's why it is
definitely
400 million times and
you all right what happens about this the
policy premium for example is for these 15
years and you have taken the payment
okay so you
appoint and a little so you feel that you have to
[music]
okay okay you should appoint
subscribe
okay the benefits you can get top
minimum should be more than ₹2000
and you cannot take as much as Tata But as much as
equal to Austria's PM
means you
cannot take school so you can take today's topic
you mean
subscribe subscribe
definitely can be
subscribe
entry now you can see that it is
90 maximum
from Ayodhya to 125 okay after that one and a half
benefit more details okay
how much benefits do you get in life and in this
policy
how much money will you get after death
you have seven times from the time of adoption
or
if there is fiber on the time left  It will be given to you
if
after taking the Yog VIDEO policy of 11212, when the
scooter keeps running, do
not forget to subscribe to it, it will remain subscribed,
suppose your market
value is low then you will get less money, that
means you get loss, the market is running, if
you are continuing for more years
then you definitely get profit,
okay, but you should not feel that
you have invested in Marg Aaj Market Joker
from 9 News, a
customer now in 2019, okay, now you bought it in school, at
that time, that means what does it mean to
subscribe to the channel, that
means you are
investing regularly and you
ever feel that you
want to withdraw money from it, that means and you do
not have to cancel it, but you have the requirement of money,
when you
score, you can subscribe to your 21
subscribers,
20 per
unit,
but the
appointed commission has
appointed the policy from each other and you and
in hatred of this,
if your policy remains in force,
okay, you can still take it, what
happens sometimes  Please subscribe if after you
stop paying your policy premium
you subscribe after completing it from the market
and if
you do not subscribe, if you want cash withdrawal then subscribe
to the market then money will be deposited
because the
subscriber is
put in it, okay there you
get simple interest on the report but you are getting a
discount, you should disconnect it,
okay this is
only for Thursday, if you want money
in the policy
subscribe
and
statement, it will end,
then you can withdraw it in a little less time,
that option is there, okay
and its unlimited free switch between the
funds, okay if you have invested in it, as I
told you, from this point onwards, when you wish,
your money will fall which I have set
and this portfolio is called
14.5, if you have
invested in it, then
subscribe means you have
invested
if it is less
and for the second one there is a
huge
profit, if you had
subscribed
then  Use the profit so that you
can invest in income funds. If the market goes down, your
money won't go down that much. The
market does fall, but the
patience in income funds is not that great in the government sector. So,
those advantages are there. If you
want to manage the switch, it's not that you can invest
unlimitedly. Now, when your
money is invested
in the market by the appointed commission,
where is the money
in the market? If you want, you can invest in the market. But you want
[music]
total subscription.
But how will it be for you?
Change import
police adhesive. Okay, so you can change this in the policy.
Okay, so if you have
seen it and you find out that you are
not able to do it, then
you can change it. If the
police wants a different option, then you
cannot subscribe to this point. You have to
talk to the police soon, but you
can change the
age reservation in it.
Suppose, when you
take the policy, then you tell that this point is
in income or this is the result in the government sector,
you put the money in it and
In the future, you feel that whatever you
will repair, in which market should your fund
go, you will have to decide this, you can
change this in the policy at any time,
your policy should be active, it is a
prediction,
what should you understand in this, in this you have to keep in mind
that whatever you should be
in the appointed village, okay, then you have to
decide this, this
subscription option because this
subscription, apart from this, the
company manager will appoint,
okay, so you cannot take pressure in that,
but if you want to take it, then you can
fix it by doing play services, then you
can feel it yourself, okay, I
told you this, in this policy,
apart from the rules, if you have to make a small investment,
then suppose you have taken a policy
for 15 years, you have paid 5 years' premium,
one year's premium is used for one or two years,
now suppose you have just
paid your premium in the last month, right now
you do not have DP, but the market is a
little down and you feel that you should make
more profit in the future, if you have a
lot of money now, then what will you do, you
want to buy a new policy?  So instead of doing that,
you can put that money in this policy. The
minimum top up is ₹2000, so
you
cannot put more than the premium you have paid.
Here I told you that you have
spent 21 years in the rebellion against the youth, so
you have to spend two lakhs every year,
so you can put more than 2 lakhs
in your policy, for that
you can put a top up after doing 3 years of the policy,
but you feel that you have got ₹5000
and you currently have ₹5000 and you want to do it one more time, then if
you have taken it from this point
and it is
of the company, then what happens is that you will
not
subscribe, but
if you
subscribe to [music]
and you
subscribe to [music], then you will top up, then its
pass will remain your parcel or
parcel from top up, okay, so anyone who is
logged in on the dhota portal, then if
you want to
cancel the entire policy after 15 years, but if you do
not
want to cancel any topic, then that is when  He should subscribe,
like and if you are subscribing then
you
are a village but the company has said that
we cannot give you Jethu's 50 thousand rupees right now, on
this topic Kavya, if
you withdraw after 5 years from the Lokayukta update
then the topic of calculations will be given in
detail but whatever amount has been offered on the current date,
you will get that 20% of that, if the top up leaves you with odd time,
okay and in this and
what else is popular in Fazilka,
you can do it, okay,
okay, increase or decrease in Assam, if
you feel that you want to increase
or decrease the policy period, then you can inform,
it depends on the time volume, I have given you the
maximum time, that time
cannot be increased, that is the minimum,
if you have given two, you feel that too
many mobile recharges are dangerous, then you
can reduce it, you
can add more to it if it is more, okay,
what should be the minimum, okay, you can
increase it,
but it should be within your means, you
can increase it, but the
payment you have appointed should not be less  You can
subscribe but this
subscription but because you have to do
everything with the companies,
you have to do that, the company will do it
but you have to
subscribe and it will be there by
selling your number of units, that is, if your
number of units is less then you need it from there, that is
why you can get it for free also,
okay now if you are doing it as I told you,
okay, then
your money is looted in the portfolio, there are aloe
vera flowers in it, you have to
select that also and
tell them that I should be subscribed
and whatever photo of mine you want,
subscribe and
subscribe from this, only then you have to
tell that you want the location, that is, the
policy you are doing on Android, then
you have to change any of these four robbers,
but
more
location means
how much should the subscription be, you have to
subscribe this, then that
market question, you have got normal profit,
okay, so
here you earn money, but that ticket flower
and east north soil house, when your
Eid will be, how much percentage will it be, only then
this will happen to you, then
if tempered glass scooter  Either you
subscribe and
if you subscribe your money will also go up and down,
subscribe,
definitely
here other means
try the skin but when will you worry about ten
percent contemplation of, only then this trick is done, in this
you have to
subscribe to the companies so through this all
your options are given here, if I
tell you here, if you are not able to
understand here, then
see here that war, then do
not forget to subscribe to my channel,
subscribe, that are
given in this policy, okay, so you will have to choose
any of these,
how will you choose, then you
will open it on the Purusha Mriga website, it is here,
okay, here at the bottom if
there will be an option, fund allocation, here
a meta,
yes yes, a
punch, a fund value
top off,
that should be here, you will take the fund, so
friend,
switch check
management diplomas, see in it, you
can see it on the front in Thomas, you will give it here by the
name of the policy, here you will
give it by the name of all the policies, here  If you want to
select your policy,
see here how many fronts are there in Blue Chip Equity, so many
fruits
are available in Equity, maximum buried India friends,
so many fans' demand should be taken here, you
can take so many fronts in the fund, there are
so many points in the debt from 3 funds, okay, you
can take this also and if you are going to
see the plane, no, I
want the office, its festival is fixed price,
okay, so it was started in 2019, you
can see here in 2015,
okay,
this is a new head of Meghnad, you will appoint the
number, you live in the same,
thank you, it is a new fund, a
new manager comes to manage it, he is asking for -
now it is running at ₹10, it is not cheap,
okay, you can add this in the comment also,
okay, if the guest
youth was born
in 2011, at that time the market was in 2011
till the correction, so to
subscribe, subscribe for a long time,
your entire
appointed
subscription remains, it does not become,
okay, then you can subscribe from here,
okay  So this message is to
tell you that your funds are available, so
you will be able to see it in it, okay and in which
year if you subscribe here from balance fund,
as I told you, okay
equity fund balance friends, I told
you, okay infertility, you should subscribe to some such
zinc, this fund portfolio with
sexual flashlight
and after that you should
subscribe, okay and after that you should
subscribe and the return is
great, meaning you will be able to stay and there is no
problem, according to that,
school means a lot, so you should
subscribe to this, so
subscribe that this experiment should
not be done, if you subscribe
and your meaning is
that the arrival keeps happening,
one means it keeps shrinking, but in less,
you do not get much trick, you will get market,
so from here you will keep
subscribing to this village,
and
station station means there is
no problem, it is available in the market,
so this half limited,
its premium paying term has to be
subscribed at all, if you have got
subscribed
from the market then you get 11 lakhs
Okay,
Galaxy's 100 most
powerful for example, if you subscribe, if you do
n't understand,
you won't get appointed
because if you
subscribe, then that
village subscribe,
Agni subscribe,
okay,
secondly, there is such an illustration of the customer writer
and this dead family, married woman,
next Arjun, you know,
maybe a gymnast, I mean, let me tell you again,
management means if you have a
table and your wife's name is in the nomination, then
if there is some dispute in your family
or you feel that you
should get your pension and no one else will
get it, then what happens at that time, if you
get your money at that time, then do
not forget to subscribe to that other family
and subscribe to the
use or any other loan instructor, here
you have taken a loan, you
mortgage your policy to the loan provider
for security that I have insurance, this is my
so much money, for security you
put it on the follow, put it for quality, in that the
person who says that I have it,
give me my money, then it repeats
there  No, the loan is yours, but there is a
division in this route, it will go to
Pacific, so this is even
better. There are
four sponsorship Anmol Kshan
charges like it happens in this, there are no
charges in the front, it is definitely
organized, you do not get to know,
okay, different, I have four, like
here in focus, if you have put
focus on soil,
how much duty is charged for it, 1.3 percent, this is your
amendment, you have this
appointed
receiver who takes your money every month or year, whatever,
one and a half, and gives it to
you there, that
means you should subscribe for that much money, if there is a
problem then India Group
wants all these equity funds,
police admit on which this is
Paramanandswaroop addition in your mind at 12120,
okay, this question will keep coming from your phone,
suppose you do
not have even ₹10, if you
want Ghrini Surya, then
you should subscribe
to such a channel from here,
if you feel like it, then you have subscribed
and
appointed the appointment.
You will follow for ₹1 and time leaving 10
lakh rupees, so time goes on - fund value means
your own money, okay, so
how much time was given to you, then subscribe on this festival of company
subscription,
here I will tell you
how much it gives you,
suppose this is your word
from 35 years, you are okay 28 and your motor charges are
one thousand above, then
how much do you have, understand that
you do not have
divided into
two,
definitely
subscribe
and if you do
not subscribe, but if you
subscribe 30,
quot 10, then you will keep getting this 19 - then it is not a
good thing, if not then you
can understand and you will get it later, but
sometimes customers come and
subscribe, so to keep
subscribing, as if you feel
that I will
subscribe, then
you get subscription to the channel, you
subscribe in it, then subscribe
10 to 15
liuji and you used to stay with me during this time,
then appointed
Delhi, anyway, if you want to cancel, you
can also cancel, but no motors will give
you  You will get a refund. You can see on this table
how much it is charging for how many years.
This motor recharges diet
means - 112 which
it does
and what else is there to talk about in this. The
soul SAA
is the same as the motor charges which continue
like 4. Yes, okay, distance which we will
talk about. Suppose you have submitted the first year's pass.
This year is over. The
second year's dua is over. Now the second year's
dua is over. You don't have 1 lakh rupees.
You have 1 lakh rupees for free. So
which college will you get from this. Now here,
more money will be there in the past few days. So
if it is fifty rupees, it is
okay. If you do not have enough money for the second year, it will be very
soon. So, the
company
appointed
subscription means
and how much is 10 rupees. Okay, then 2002 rupees. Okay, here
for Rauniyar Vaishya Sthal, okay, it is
okay
that
in 300 pages it has been said that I will pay up to 5000 rupees, so it is
5,000 rupees, so you can spend more than half of it.
10 -
- - - If it is
years then you will be appointed here and you should
subscribe to the pregnancy then the pregnancy will be with them
till the completion of the pregnancy,
here you have one thing
left, suppose you do not have money,
after 6 minutes the money will go to you, okay then
what will they do, then you will
give the appointments to the quick appointment, then this will be given to you from the market
and you should
subscribe.
If you
stop subscribing, if you want to do anything then you can cancel it by paying the
Biscuit Charges Cash as I told you, if you
do then you can get it cancelled by getting the
premium cancelled, you can
find out the same password in the continuation but
you will be charged the same amount,
unmute the PM dish, okay
and the policy revival is done in this country, then
you can revise it, to revise,
you have a revival time of five years, which
means you have to
revise it before the policy expires, you used the first year of your policy for 2 years, did
not make the payment for the second year, left the second year for 2 years,
then you do
not have money to pay for the second year, even last year you do
not have money to pay, 14 years are very
much, 45 lakhs, then you can activate it by putting the full amount,
but
what is mostly free, plate, if you are not subscribed, if you have
not subscribed, then
subscribe, which is
15 days for gas per AR Rahman in the market,
unit pricing, unit president means there is
a page of market share, it
speaks from the market  And in this nomination when there are
followers and nothing else in it, there is no
rickshaw, nothing, okay, the word R,
in this policy all your benefits,
so if you
want to buy the card then tell me in the comment in this box,
thank you for pressing the subscribe button on the channel